[
    {
        "question": "Skopje is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Macedonia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country borders Macedonia to the east?",
        "answer": "Bulgaria"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country borders Macedonia to the west?",
        "answer": "Albania"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country borders Macedonia to the south?",
        "answer": "Greece"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country borders Macedonia to the north?",
        "answer": "Serbia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Qeru Chay is a village in which country?",
        "answer": "Iran"
    },
    {
        "question": "Reaching 20,320 feet (6,194 meters) above sea level, Denali is located in what US state?",
        "answer": "Alaska"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the deepest land gorge in the US?",
        "answer": "Along the border of eastern Oregon, eastern Washington and western Idaho"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where would you find the `Lone Cypress`?",
        "answer": "Pebble Beach, California"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state receives the most annual rainfall?",
        "answer": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US state is nicknamed `The Ocean State`?",
        "answer": "Rhode Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "What Ivy League University is located in New Haven, Connecticut?",
        "answer": "Yale University"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Gila River flows into what river?",
        "answer": "Colorado River"
    },
    {
        "question": "Staten Island is part of what city?",
        "answer": "New York"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Delaware River flows into what bay?",
        "answer": "Delaware Bay"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to the Pebble Beach Golf Links?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Redwood National Park is located in which US state?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is nicknamed the `Golden State`?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state is home to Joshua Tree National Park?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state`s official flower is the orange blossom?",
        "answer": "Florida"
    },
    {
        "question": "Salton Sea is located in which western US state?",
        "answer": "California"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was New York`s Bedloe`s Island renamed in 1956?",
        "answer": "Liberty Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river flows through the Grand Canyon?",
        "answer": "The Colorado River"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country is Phnom Penh the capital of?",
        "answer": "Cambodia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Phnom Penh is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Cambodia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Phnom Penh is the capital of which Asian country?",
        "answer": "Cambodia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Cambodia?",
        "answer": "Phnom Penh"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country shares a land border with Cambodia to the east?",
        "answer": "Vietnam"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Gulf is located southwest of Cambodia?",
        "answer": "Gulf of Thailand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which fruit is called `halakahiki` in Hawaiian and has been grown in Hawaii since the early 1800`s?",
        "answer": "Pineapples"
    },
    {
        "question": "The 1979 Soviet invasion of what nearby nation caused an international uproar?",
        "answer": "Afghanistan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the capital of India before New Delhi?",
        "answer": "Calcutta"
    },
    {
        "question": "How would one describe Tierra del Fuego?",
        "answer": "An archipelago"
    },
    {
        "question": "Into which body of water does the Yukon River discharge?",
        "answer": "Bering Sea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the orange color on Ireland`s flag represent?",
        "answer": "Protestants"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the easternmost Caribbean country?",
        "answer": "Barbados"
    },
    {
        "question": "The Ghirardelli Chocolate Company was founded in which city?",
        "answer": "San Francisco, California"
    },
    {
        "question": "Between which two African countries is there a land that no one owns?",
        "answer": "Egypt and Sudan"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the record snowfall in Phoenix, Arizona?",
        "answer": "One inch"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of the US state of Tennessee?",
        "answer": "Nashville"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Antigua and Barbuda?",
        "answer": "St. John`s"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which famous actor is honored with a statue in Leicester Square?",
        "answer": "Charlie Chaplin"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which North American city would you find Joe Shuster Way?",
        "answer": "Toronto"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the avenue that lies between 12th and 14th Avenue in San Francisco?",
        "answer": "Funston Avenue"
    },
    {
        "question": "`Friday the 13th motorcycle rally` is held on every Friday the 13th in what Canadian city?",
        "answer": "Port Dover"
    },
    {
        "question": "What island does the Statue of Liberty stand on?",
        "answer": "Liberty Island"
    },
    {
        "question": "The beaver is the national emblem of which country?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "Albert Einstein was offered the position of prime minister of what country?",
        "answer": "Israel"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is the capital of Mississippi?",
        "answer": "Jackson"
    },
    {
        "question": "The International Headquarters of the United Nations is surrounded by what city?",
        "answer": "New York City"
    }
]